http://www.aggreko.com/en-us/privacy

Home
Castle.Proxies.IBreadcrumbSettingsProxy?.BreadcrumbMobileText
Privacy notice
Privacy notice
The following sets out the Data Privacy Policy (the "Policy") for Aggreko plc ("Aggreko") and the manner in which Aggreko collects, uses and stores personal data and information submitted to it by its subscribers and/or users of its website ("you") ("your").
Aggreko operates a global website. It can be found at www.aggreko.com but can also be accessed in certain countries via national domain name addresses. The Aggreko website is translated into various languages for accessibility by users in certain countries.
For the purposes of reference, the data controller is Aggreko plc (registered number SC177553) of 8th Floor, 120 Bothwell Street, Glasgow, Lanarkshire, G2 7JS.
This policy is to be read in conjunction with Aggreko's legal statement and in accessing and using Aggreko's website; you confirm that you have read and understand this Policy and that you consent to the collection and use of your personal information and details by Aggreko in accordance with this Policy. If you wish at any time to withdraw your consent, please notify the Head of Data Privacy at the email address set out in this Policy.
1. PRIVACY POLICY
Aggreko is committed to protecting the privacy of those who use its website, and the confidentiality of any personal information or details submitted or provided to it by you.
2. WHAT TYPE OF INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT
(a) If you contact us using one of our websites we may request and/or require further information about you or your company, including, but not limited to, your name, your company’s name, address, telephone and facsimile number, email address and other identity and contact information.
(b) If you use our services, request quotes for products through our websites or otherwise make use of the websites, we may ask you to provide further information, including but not limited to technical specifications, financial information, and other business related information.
(c) When you visit our website, we may collect certain routing information such as Internet Protocol address of your originating Internet Service Provider, and information provided by “cookies” stored on your hard drive. Cookies are small data files containing a unique identifier so that we can recognize you each time you return to our sites, and which keep track of the pages you view on the website and which services you use (you can find further details on cookies in our Cookie Policy).
(d) We may also collect aggregate information about the use of our website, including which pages are most frequently visited, how many visitors we receive daily, and how long visitors stay on each page.
3. USE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
Any personal information or details you provide to Aggreko on this website will be treated and kept in confidence, but may be used by Aggreko in the following ways:
(a) Where you have provided your contact details in order to receive information from Aggreko, we may use your contact information to let you know about the products or services we offer (including online reports and newsletters) and about enhancements or changes to the website. We may also use your data to enable Aggreko to respond to complaints, or to form management decisions regarding the future development of its website.
(b) If you indicated your consent on the e-mail submission page, Aggreko may also use your personal data for future mailings in relation to the subject of interest that you identified on the email contact page or the needs analysis page, in relation to support and/or new products or services that may be relevant to you. You can unsubscribe from this at any time by clicking on the "unsubscribe" link on any e-mail we send to you or by contacting us at the detailed at the end of this Notice.
(c)
Where you have provided personal information for the purposes of potential employment with Aggreko, you agree that Aggreko, members of the Aggreko group or non-affiliated companies who perform support services on Aggreko’s behalf may use the information submitted on the Careers/Current Vacancies page of this website for the purposes of processing your application. Aggreko may also use your personal data to notify you of job openings within Aggreko which may be of interest to you. The information you provide on the application form will be kept on file by Aggreko in our CV management system for a period of six (6) months from the date of submission. If after that period no job has been matched to the information you provided, your personal information will be deleted from our database. If you are contacted directly by Aggreko's Human Resources department after the date of submission of your CV, Aggreko will be bound by the relevant legislation regarding the retention of your CV on its database during the period when it is considering hiring or employing you and if you are employed, during your employment period.
4. WITH WHOM DO WE SHARE INFORMATION?
(a) We may provide the information we collect about you and your company, including your e-mail address or other identifying information, to our Affiliates and to third parties, including manufacturers, suppliers or others involved in the distribution chain to provide the products or services that have been requested. We may provide aggregate statistics about visitors, website transactions or other website activity.
(b) We may disclose information about you or your company if we have a good faith belief that we are required to do so by law or legal process; to respond to claims; or to protect your vital interests or the vital interest of others
Transfer of your personal data outside if the European Economic Area (EEA)
If we require to transfer your personal data outside the EEA we will ensure that the recipient agrees to provide the same or similar level of protection as we do and that they only use your personal data in accordance with our instructions.
How long do we keep this information about you?
We keep information in line with our data retention schedule which provides that no personal data is retained for a period longer than is necessary for the particular business purpose unless we are required to retain the personal information in order to meet our legal and regulatory requirements. In all cases our need to use your personal information will be assessed on a regular basis and information that is no longer required will be securely deleted.
5. DATA SUBJECT RIGHTS
In some circumstances the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) grants you certain rights in relation to your data.  These rights are detailed below along with details of how we will respond in circumstances where these rights apply.
Subject access requests
You may have the right to access particular personal data that we hold about you. This is referred to as a subject access request. In circumstances where these rights apply we will respond promptly, and certainly within one month from the point of receiving the request and all necessary information from you. Our formal response will include details of the personal data we hold about you, including the following:
- sources from which we acquired the information;
- the purposes for processing the information; and
- persons or entities with whom we have shared the information.
Right to rectification
You may have the right to the rectification of any inaccurate personal data we hold concerning you. Taking into account the purposes of the processing, you may have the right to have incomplete personal data completed, including by means of providing a supplementary statement.
Right to erasure
You may have the right to the erasure of your personal data without undue delay.
Right to restriction of processing
You may have the right to restrict the processing of your personal data where one of the following applies:
a) your personal data is inaccurate; the processing is unlawful and you oppose to the erasure of the personal data;
b) you have objected to us processing your personal data whilst we verify whether there are legitimate grounds for the processing activity.
Notification obligation regarding rectification or erasure of personal data or restriction of processing
Where we rectify, erase, or restrict the processing of any personal data, we will notify this to any third parties to whom we have shared the personal information unless this is impossible or involves disproportionate effort.
Right to data portability
You may have the right to receive your personal data in a structured, commonly used and machine readable format for transmission to another data controller.
Right to object
You may have the right to object, at any time, to the processing of your personal data, including any personal profiling: unless this relates to processing that is necessary for a task carried out in the public interest or an exercise of official authority vested in us. In this circumstance we will cease processing  your personal data unless we can demonstrate compelling legitimate grounds for the processing.
Right to not be subject to decisions based solely on automated processing
We do not carry out any automated processing, which may lead to an automated decision based on your personal data.
Accuracy of information
In order to provide excellent customer service, it is important that we hold accurate personal data about you. We take reasonable steps to ensure the accuracy of any personal data or sensitive information we obtain. We ensure that the source of any personal data or sensitive information is clear and we carefully consider any challenges to the accuracy of the information. We also consider when it is necessary to update the information, such as name or address changes and you can help us by informing us of these when they occur.
6. FURTHER INFORMATION
If you have a complaint
If you have a complaint regarding the use of your personal data or sensitive information then please contact our Head of Data Privacy: DataPrivacy@aggreko.co.uk
If your complaint is not resolved to your satisfaction you may wish to make a formal complaint to your local data regulator.  You also have the right to appoint a third party to lodge a complaint on your behalf and exercise your right to seek compensation.
Chat Policy:
What information do we collect?
Aggreko stores and processes personal data of its customers while using LiveChat. We store such data as: first name, last name, e-mail address, phone number, IP number, browser information, operating system, geolocation (and other information as listed above on our Privacy page).
How long do we keep this information about you?
We keep information in line with our data retention schedule which provides that no personal data is retained for a period longer than is necessary for the particular business purpose unless we are required to retain the personal information in order to meet our legal and regulatory requirements. In all cases our need to use your personal information will be assessed on a regular basis and information that is no longer required will be securely deleted.
How my personal data are used/processed in a LiveChat Transcript? How can I execute my right to be forgotten?
We process your personal data only in for purposes listed in our Privacy Policy. We do not sell your data. Aggreko stores transcripts of your chat history.  You can freely decide whether you want to have your chats permanently deleted from a system. Then just send us a request at Dataprivacy@aggreko.co.uk and we will delete your data within 30 days. (When sending us the request, note that it should be sent from the email address that is registered under your LiveChat Transcript subscription. Also, don’t forget to include your first name, last name and phone number.)
Tell us what you need
We’ll help you find what’s right for you
844-550-3618
Contact Us
Share This
